Why did you come?
I think... I want to be forgiven
more than anything
By whom?
I never blamed you
not once
You came for me
that's all that matters
How many sleepless nights must we count
Before we finally arrive?
How many lives must be lost
Before the fighting comes to an end?
Just helpless clowns
Tumbling through history
Like someone once said
The answer is blowin' in the wind
How many times must our turned-away faces be struck
Before we stop pretending not to notice?
How much suffering must we endure
Before a smile can be free?
Bound by rusted chains
If we run away with our tails between our legs again
Like someone once said
The answer is blowin' in the wind
With a voice strained to its limit
And with tightly clenched hands
Destiny is surely waiting for its time to change
With the modest power of a tiny love
Sorrow is always
Waiting to be held
Rearranging a puzzle of lies
Pitiful swindlers
Clumsily acting skillful
Foolish romanticists
A premonition of a day coming
When history falls silent
Like someone once said
The answer is blowin' in the wind
With a voice strained to its limit
And with tightly clenched hands
Destiny is surely waiting for its time to change
With the modest power of a tiny love
Sorrow is always
Waiting to be held